Oh, I'm going to just block you and you don't got to be bothered with me at all.
Come in here talking about I get you riled up.
Bitch, get the fuck out of my Instagram name.
So tomorrow is a general strike taking place here in the United States.
This means the goal is to not spend any money if you can to not go to work.
And to be quite honest, how do I put this?
Okay, tomorrow is a test run.
How many people in here are not going to work or calling out?
This person said I think she was playing.
I don't know her to play with me like that.
I'm a literal person.
So unless we're friends and we have an ongoing joke, keep that shit tucked.
So the realist in me needs to inform you that for a strike to be effective, it has to be continual.
So I don't want people to necessarily feel disheartened if there are not any gains created after tomorrow that are visible.
However, the necessity for tomorrow is to basically demonstrate, not for the government, but for each other, that it can be done.
That's really what this is about.
If, I mean, I don't know, maybe the organizers have a different point of view.
But for me, when I'm looking at it, I'm like, oh, that's what this is about.
This is about demonstrating for each other what a strike is.
And if you are going to spend money tomorrow, at the very least, spend cash.
Now, I was going to make my book, my new release, go on sale tomorrow, but I'm not because it's the strike.
Someone asked, why are we doing a general strike?
I'm hoping you're asking that rhetorically.
A general strike has been planned because the United States is a collapsing empire that is draining the citizens of this country on its way out.
This is being done by the central banking systems and the IMF, who control the United States and Europe and Israel, et cetera, et cetera.
The idea of a general strike is to demonstrate the power of the people, the power of the ruling class by withholding our presence monetarily and in labor.
Unfortunately, this doesn't necessarily have the efficacy that many would like to see unless it is upheld for an extended amount of time.
However, because the United States has been under the repression of a psychological operation for the past 60 years that has brainwashed everybody to indoctrination and indoctrinated them to believe that this country is infallible, that this country is protecting them, et cetera, et cetera.
We are behind in being able to actually defend ourselves.
Now, May Day is Labor Day for the rest of the world.
So May 1st for the globe is Labor Day.
Labor Day is a day of paying regard to unions, to the organized unions of laborers, which, as we have seen throughout colonization, has become incredibly necessary for even a semblance of protections.
And policies for the working class.
So May Day for the world is tomorrow.
The United States does not celebrate May Day the same day as the world because, of course, the United States does not want Americans, U.S.ians, so to speak, to be in alignment with the globe.
So, someone here asked, are we not paying rent and bills collectively?
And this is what I would like to tell you.
If you need everybody to do it for you not to, it will never get done.
You're not desperate enough.
You'll say to yourself, no, it's not that.
It's just that I'm, you know, I can't put myself in a bad situation, et cetera.
You're not desperate enough.
And that might be the case.
You might not be desperate enough.
However, at some point, the desperation, I hope, will do one of two things, or both.
It will encourage you to live by your own individual morals and principles, regardless of whoever else is joining you.
And or two, it will encourage you to organize people around you to do the same.
Now, someone asked, why any desperation at all?
And that's a dumb question, so I'm not even going to address it.
So, when I see folks tomorrow saying, I'm staying home, kudos to you.
When I see folks tomorrow saying, I'm not spending any money, kudos to you.
When I see folks tomorrow saying, you know, I'm doing the best with the situation I'm in, kudos to you.
Abby, I do not need you to come with the asterisk.
Some folks don't have a choice.
Obviously, this is not relevant to them.
Obviously, this is not applicable to you if you don't have a choice.
The other part of it is, everyone has a choice.
Everyone has a choice.
Everyone.
The repercussions of your choices are different for everyone.
However, everyone has a choice.
And we continuously push this narrative that people don't have a choice.
Everyone has a choice.
If you're threatened with death, you still have a choice.
And some people have chosen, fuck it, then I guess I'm going to die.
If you're threatened with losing your job, if you're threatened with going to prison,
if you're threatened with homeless, like, everyone has a choice.
The question becomes, what is the choice?
And how are you navigating it?
So, that concept of not everyone has a choice is inaccurate.
Everyone has a choice.
Everyone does not have the same circumstances.
Everyone does not have the same set of outcomes.
But everyone has a choice.
You know, I think a lot of people don't realize that death is not a bottom line for everybody.
Death is not a breaking point for everybody.
For some people, if the option is, well, you might die, they're like, well, it ain't like it's so great here anyway.
So, we find ourselves at a time where what's happening in the United States has been happening because of the United States all over the globe.
This is the Imperial Boomerang.
So, people are talking about Section 8 because Section 8 is how many people exist.
Section 8 is how many people subsist, I mean to say, sorry.
So, all of us have different things impacting us in different ways.
However, I would suffice to say that at this point, everyone is being impacted in some shape, way, or form by the collapse of the United States as the head of empire.
Again, empire is not collapsing.
The United States as the head of empire is collapsing.
Empire is not collapsing because enough of us aren't understanding what the concept of empire is.
Empire is not collapsing because enough of us are not willing to actually take out the powerful.
And I'll include myself in that.
You know, it's not like I'm running up on, it's not like I'm running up on these people's houses and burning them down.
Empire is not crumbling because too many people, in my opinion, are not willing to expand their consciousness beyond the singularity of George, I mean, of Donald Trump as a bad guy.
It's much easier to just simply focus with a myopic mindset that that's the bad guy.
Thank you, Sarah.
Much easier.
Even though it's exponentially clear that there are, I can't believe we're in 2026 and you're talking about friends refusing to support Kamala.
I hope they're not friends with you anymore.
The concept that it is our responsibility to support someone who supports genocide and not their responsibility to actively speak against genocide in order to gain our support is exactly the issue for why empire continues to exist.
You all keep putting these people, even when you can't see them, you are honoring them.
Tomorrow, here in the United States, there is a general strike.
The purpose of the general strike is to be in allegiance and alignment with Labor Day that is being celebrated around the world,
with a consciousness around the protection of workers, with a consciousness around the power of the workers.
We are what make the world go round.
And someone here saying Kamala was the better of the two evils.
Y'all are so ridiculous with that that I can't even wrap my head around it, so I'm not going to try to.
The fact that people have actively accepted, well, if the only two options are evil and evil, I'll just take the nicer evil.
That is slave mentality.
That's what that is.
And I want to remind you that Harriet Tubman's husband, who was a free man, told her,
you know, I don't think you should run away.
I don't think you should run away because the devil you know is better than the devil you don't.
And at least you know this master.
You don't know who you're going to get if you get captured.
I love the country that my black ancestors have built, but I low-key would like to see America fail in a way
that forces us to assimilate to other cultures around the world, not in a colonial way.
I don't love the country that our ancestors built.
I love the culture.
I love the customs.
That's about it.
I mean, I like, like, you know, the scenery, you know, the national parks and whatnot.
So again, tomorrow we have the opportunity to, you ain't scared of the devil you don't know or the devil, you know, Amanda,
why did you put my name in all caps?
Why and how are you so brave to say whatever you want like this?
I'm just saying the truth.
I'm not even saying like opinions.
The real question is why is everybody so afraid to say the truth?
Yana, I'm not special in that regard.
Like, I mean, many people have said the truth.
They've written the truth.
They've performed the truth.
They've painted the truth.
I am fully aware that the truth is the only thing that will set us free.
Yes, I'm familiar with Angie Dixon.
I literally just posted her on my page.
Stop typing in all caps on here.
I don't like being yelled at.
So again, I want to encourage anybody who is here that is available tomorrow.
Sorry.
I want to encourage anybody who is unaware to take part in tomorrow's general strike.
Do not spend any money.
If you can call out of work, call out.
There are entire school districts that are shutting down for tomorrow.
As a show, as a demonstration of resistance.
So if you're not aware on like what's going on tomorrow, look around on the internets, right here on social media.
Do a quick catch up and understand that tomorrow is about showing each other.
How much power we can have when we get together, when we get behind each other.
Globally, tomorrow is Labor Day.
It's May Day.
In the United States, tomorrow we are on a general strike.
I hope this helps.